# KATHARINA REMPE AZANZA

## UX / UI DESIGNER AND CREATIVE DIRECTOR

I'm a UX/UI designer with a background in F&B, retail and hospitality. Experienced in negotiating and communicating with different kinds of clients, employers, and customers. Skilled in optimizing work processes, brand visuals, and communication to enhance user experiences.

## EXPERIENCE

## FOUNDER, VP MARKETING, CREATIVE DIRECTOR, UX/UI DESIGNER

JUJU EATS / FEELGOOD INC . 2010-PRESENT

- Designed and managed the Juju Eats e-commerce user experience and design interface platforms.
- Created the Juju brand book / style guides and is responsible that all marketing collateral is aligned with brand guidelines.
- Designed all marketing collateral including menu boards, posters, brochures, take-out bags, food labels, product packaging, and crew uniforms.
- Product styling and photography for internal marketing, and other media purposes.
- Managed all Juju social media accounts, and public relations needs.
- Conceptualized, designed, formulated and brought to market the Juju Cleanse Detox kits.
- Designed the interior spaces for all Juju Eats salad bar branches, and kiosks.

#### **DESIGN & BRANDING CONSULTANT**

THE FARM AT SAN BENITO · 1998-2008

- Consulted on design decisions affecting all aspects of operations of The Farm, including architectural, landscape, packaging, merchandising, interior design, marketing material, and branding.
- Product styling and photography for internal marketing, and other media purposes.

#### CREATIVE DIRECTOR FOR RETAIL

BERDE PLANTS INC · 1997-2007

- Interior decoration and visual merchandising of four retail outlets.
- Managed special events division: Designed and coordinated the decoration of banquets, weddings, etc. with large hotels and special events planners.
- Designed booths and visual display for international trade shows in Manila, Singapore, Germany, France, China and the United States.
- Designed the annual product catalogues, and styled product photography.

### CONTACT

- https://www.behance.net/katazanza
- kat.azanza@gmail.com
- +63-917-533-7349
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/katharina-rempe-azanza-306998121/

## UX/UI SKILLS

User Research
Competitor Analysis
User Flows
Wireframing
Prototyping
Usability Testing
Brand Identity
Design Guidelines
Interface Design

### **TOOLS**

Adobe XD
Illustrator
Photoshop
Sketch
Figma
Balsamiq
InVision

#### **EDUCATION**

# BA. LANDSCAPE ARCHITECTURE

Kingston University 1993-1997 • London, UK

#### UX/UI DESIGN CERTIFICATE

Career Foundry 2021 • Berlin, Germany

## LANGUAGES

English German Tagalog